<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<languages>

  <English>
  


      <string name="PRESENTATION">Hello and welcome to Multi-Language System</string>
      <string name="SAMPLE_TEXT_1">Here you can have some text (1).</string>
      <string name="SAMPLE_TEXT_2">Here you can have some different text (2).</string>
      <string name="SAMPLE_TEXT_3">Here you can\nhave\nanother\ndifferent multi-line\ntext (3).</string>

      <string name="MESSAGE_HEADER">MESSAGE:</string>

      <string name="DOWNLOAD_BUTTON">Download</string>
      <string name="POLITIC_BUTTON">Privacy policy</string>
      <string name="INSTRUCTION_BUTTON">Instruction</string>
      <string name="SUPPORT_VERSIONS_BUTTON">Support versions</string>
      <string name="EXIT_BUTTON">Exit</string>

      <string name="CANCEL_BUTTON">Back</string>
      <string name="CONFIRM_BUTTON">Confirm</string>

      <string name="DESCRIPTION">If you liked the Aether Dragon add-on - link, you will definitely like the Dragon Mounts mod, which will increase the number of dragons in the game. Four new dragons, three types of new armor and weapons - all this will appear immediately after installing the add-on.

Dragons got their own armor, skin and sword. The only exception is the Phantom Dragon, that we will talk about at the end of the article. To dress the dragon in armor, use a long press. A saddle, trunk, and horse armor per horse are used in the same way.

Dragons are given both a hostile and a tame version. The distinction is simple-if a dragon flies, it is best to stay away from it.

Sword Crafting Recipe.

The first dragon is the Ethereal dragon, which most are already familiar with. Mob can be found in the mountains. Extremely dangerous opponent that shoots ice balls.
Health: 300
Type of Attack: Globes of Ice
Method of domestication: Golden Apple

The second dragon is the Fire dragon, adjacent to the ethereal dragon. Aggressive mob that fires fireballs.
Health: 275
Type of Attack: Fireballs
Method of domestication: Fireball

The next dragon is the Dragon of the Edge, which every user will recognize. The Mob only appears in the Edge dimension, but only the one on the ground is tamed, not the boss. Either way, you'll need a dragon egg to tame it.
Health: 200
Type of Attack: Fireballs
Method of domestication: Dragon Egg

Lastly, the Phantasmal. A beautiful and fun-looking monster that can be tamed with dice.
Health: 300
Type of Attack: Explosive Shells
Method of domestication: dice</string>

      <string name="SUPPORT_VERSIONS_LIST"></string>
      <string name="INSTRUCTION">1. Go to the addon page, download and wait for the end of the load.
2. Open the addon. Wait for the end of imports.
3. After you see the phrase "Import of the world is successfully completed," the installation is over.
4. Open the downloaded world and enjoy the game!</string>

      <string name="MESSAGE1_BUTTON">MESSAGE 1</string>
      <string name="MESSAGE2_BUTTON">MESSAGE 2</string>
      <string name="MESSAGE3_BUTTON">MESSAGE 3</string>
    
    
    
      <string name="SAMPLE_DROPDOWN_1">ENG DROP OPTION 1</string>
      <string name="SAMPLE_DROPDOWN_2">ENG DROP OPTION 2</string>
      <string name="SAMPLE_DROPDOWN_3">ENG DROP OPTION 3</string>

    
      <string name="SAMPLE_MESSAGE_1">Here you can have a message text (1).</string>
      <string name="SAMPLE_MESSAGE_2">Here you can have a different message text (2).</string>
      <string name="SAMPLE_MESSAGE_3">Here you can have another different message text (3).</string>


      <string name="GAME_HEADER">Game Scene</string>
      <string name="GAME_MESSAGE">This is like an in-game text.</string>

     
  </English>

</languages>
